副总统 第一季第4集
我到底是爲什麽要把午餐休息时间
Why on earth am I spending my lunch break
耗费在伟大的Chung州长图书发行会上?
at the great governor Chung's book launch?
至少好过看着Gary的漏勺下巴滴面汤
Because it's better than watching Gary drip that fucking noodle juice down his chin.
老天 我只想顺点酱黄瓜就走
God, I'm gonna snort a line of tzatziki and go.
我被革除"冗长辩论"的事烦得要死 连聊天都挤没了
I am so mired in filibuster reform, I've got no conversation.
- 你认识Chung吗? - 不熟
- Do you know Chung? - Not really.
- 嘿嘿! - Dan 好兄弟
- Heh-hey! - Dan, my man.
州长 很高兴见到你 老友
Governor. Good to see you, my friend.
- 你最近如何? - 非常好
- How are you, sir? - I'm very well.
- 噢 你想必是Amy了 - 正是
- Oh, and you must be Amy. - Yes.
那麽 Dan 副总统那边什麽态度?
So, Dan, how's it working out with the V.P.?
如果你愿意放下身段 我总是需要Daniel吾友帮助的
'Cause if you ever wanna step several rungs down the ladder, I could always use help from a fellow Daniel.
Dan一心只想往上爬
Dan only climbs up ladders.
对 但有时欲登极巅 须下高峰
Yes, but sometimes you have to go down to go up.
- 我猜副总统是无暇拨冗了 - 对 她表示歉意
I assume the vice president would be too busy. Yes. She sends her apologies.
她在准备"会见新闻界" (美国NBC周日采访节目)
- She's prepping for "Meet the Press." - Ah.
我则是要上"面对全国" (美国CBS采访节目)
I'll be on "Face the Nation."
但显然大家都会去给她捧场 我还是推了吧
But everyone will be watching her, so I guess I can just wing it.
- 我是不是要给她签个名? - 不... 介意
- Shall I sign a book for her? - No... 'kay.
我最好四处走走
I'd better be going around myself,
确保和每个人都打个照面
make sure everyone gets to touch the hem of my garment.
- Dan 好兄弟 - 对
Dan, the man. All right.
"欲登极巅 须下高峰"
"You have to go down to go up."
- 什麽人啊 - 这句我得留着备用
- What a jerk. - I'm gonna steal that,
人家可是口绽莲花巧舌如簧
because he who speaks in maxims.
- 能让我听着有深度 - 这个很不错 好像是玉米面包
Can sound wise. This is good. This is like cornbread.
你们好 孩子们
Hello, children.
- 你好 参议员 - 准备再找几个背后捅刀子的对象?
- Hello, senator. - You looking for some fresh backs to stab?
噢 Doyle参议员 这不过是游戏一场
Oh, senator Doyle, it's all part of the game.
是吗 告诉你 你不是想玩游戏吗 Danny?
Yeah, well, I'll tell you, you wanna play a game, Danny?
怎麽不试试用老二玩弄iPad呢?
Why don't you try working an iPad with your dick?
不行 他早就过度开发那里导致腕道症候群了 (因长期重复性动作导致的疾病)
No, he's already got carpal tunnel in that area.
你对我没什麽建设性的建议吗 Amy?
You have nothing constructive to say to me, Amy?
关于绿色産业的吗?
Is this about clean jobs?
噢 加了俩搞石油的还能这麽叫吗?
Oh, is that what they call it still with two oil guys on it?
哇 你们要买多少喷漆 才能给那坨代谢物包金衣啊
Wow, you're gonna have to buy a lot of spray cans to paint that turd gold.
人人有其权力范围 参议员 即使是副总统
Everyone has limits to their power, senator, even the vice president.
对 而我有权撤离
Yeah, and I have the power to withdraw,
这也正是我现在要做的
which is what I'm gonna do right now.
他说的撤离 他... 他不是指
When he said withdraw, he's... he's not talking about
撤离革除"冗长辩论"工作 对吧?
withdrawing from filibuster reform, though, right?
- 不! 不是吧! - 你以爲他在说什麽?
- No! No! - What do you think he's talking about?
我以爲是指他要撤离谈话
I assumed it was withdraw from the conversation.
除了天主教徒和管家谁会把撤离当动词用?
Who uses withdraw as a fuckin' verb besides catholics and butlers?
- 也就以色列军方偶尔用用 - 你以爲我不知道啊? 你少耍我
Maybe the Israeli military every once in a while. Yeah, you think I don't know? You're fucking with me.
- 少来 快走 我们回去 - 噢 不不 不行 我要留下
No. Come on, let's just head back. Oh, no, no. No way. I'm staying right here.
要办公可以用网络 对吧? Chung之变革
You gotta network to get work, baby. All right? Chung for change.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
我们有工作
We've got jobs.
- 绿色産业 - 绿色産业 革除"冗长辩论"
- Clean jobs. - Clean jobs. Filibuster reform.
- 对 重点说那个 - 好 知道我们需要什麽吗? 更寻常更亲民的话题
- Yeah, hit that hard. - Right. You know what we need? We need some normal, regular-people stuff.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
你可以谈谈聚光灯下你的上唇多麽水润
You could talk about how you always get a sweaty upper lip underneath studio lights.
展现你的寻常
That shows you're normal.
我说的绝对是完全不同的寻常 Gary
I'm really talking about a different kind of normal, Gary.
噢 好吧
Oh, okay.
最后以闲聊结尾 对吧?
Small talk's gonna happen at the end, right?
- 对 - Gregory是红人队的粉丝
- Right. - Gregory's a redskins fan.
- 他兴许会提起橄榄球 - 橄榄球
- He'll probably bring up football. - Football.
而我是个...
And I am a...
乌鸦队球迷 所以...
Ravens fan, so...
副总统女士 你的乌鸦队今年表现如何?
Madam vice president, how are your Ravens doing this year?
我家乌鸦超赞 知道原因吗
My Ravens are gold and I'll tell you why.
因爲我们有Joe Flacco做四分卫 (NFL著名球星 虽年轻但战绩斐然)
Because we have Joe Flacco as our quarterback.
- 对 对 - 而且...
- Yes, yes. - And...
红人队今年的快攻打法很不错
Well, the redskins have a great running game this year
说实话 你们那个外接员
and, honestly, that receiving corps over there,
Anquan Boldin 对你们可没啥好处
Anquan Boldin, not looking good for you.
- Anquan? - 乌鸦队的翼锋
Anquan? A receiver on the Ravens.
好吧 我怎麽可能记得住
Okay, well, I'm not gonna remember that.
- 那可不成 - 知道吗 没关系的
- That's not good. - It doesn't matter.
以啤酒的名义发誓 乌鸦铁定赢
You wanna bet a beer that the Ravens will win.
- 啤酒让我胀气 - 你也可以谈谈那个...
- Beer makes me so gassy. - You can talk about that...
关于它怎麽让你腹胀的 啤酒
about how it always bloats you, beer.
- 很赞的点子 - Chung怎麽样?
- That's a good one. - How was Chung?
他有没有做这个动作 让你不知道是该抱他 还是把他钉上十字架?
Did he do this thing where you don't know if you're supposed to hug him or crucify him?
顺便一提 我是想钉他十字架的
Which, by the way, makes me wanna crucify him.
- 我没留下听他的演讲 - 给我看看
- I did not stay for his speech. - Let me see this.
"旗开得胜" (另有同名的橄榄球纪录电影)
"The Good Fight."
- 我知道 这标题... - 拜了个托! Sue?
- I know. The title... - Puh-lease! Sue?
- 在 - 帮我处理这个
- Yep. - Handle this for me.
- 你想让我撕了它? - 对
- Do you want me to shred it? - Yeah.
- 我是不是该烧了这团狗剩? - 好
- Should I fire up the shit eater? - Yeah.
别别 先等等 他在扉页给你留了几句
No, no. Wait a second. He scrawled something in the front for you.
"致副总统Salina Meyer"...
"To vice president Salina Meyer"...
居然写成了"a"... "仰慕你的同道"
with an "a"... "from an admiring wannabe."
真是个昏蛋
What an e-hole.
- 把"昏"换成"混" - 真是堆华盛顿出品的狗剩
Changed the "a" to an "e." What a bunch of Washington bullshit that is.
我真是烦死了... 嘿 Gary 我...
I am so tired of... hey, Gary, I...
我是说 同道? 他显然是在开玩笑 对吧?
I mean, wannabe? He's obviously making a joke, right?
他不会真的以爲他有能力
He doesn't really think that he's some sort
胜任副总统竞选人吧
of credible vice presidential candidate.
唔 魅力不凡的战争英雄
Mm, charismatic war hero.
对 但我是说 总统
Yeah, but, I mean, the president
总是会支持现任副总统吧
always sticks with the incumbent veep.
而且 他不会让选择你变成天大的失误
Plus, he doesn't wanna look like he made a massive error picking you.
那可真可爱
Well, that was lovely.
- 他被我套牢了... 你是不是这个意思... - 我不是那个意思
- He's stuck with me... is that what... - I don't mean it like that.
我是指好的套牢 就像维系婚姻什麽的
I meant good stuck, like if your marriage lasts or whatever.
- 总统不会抛弃你的 - 你安静点行不? 怎麽...?
The president's not gonna ditch you. Would you be quiet? What...?
- 需要我派Scott收集Chung的情报吗 鉴于这些风声? - 不不不不不
Want me to have Scott put together a file on Chung, - given the noise? - No. No, no, no, no.
别让他知道你担心了 别当他是回事
Do not let him know that you're worried, do not make it a thing.
- 对 Amy 别当他是回事 好吗? - 好
- Yeah, Amy, don't make it a thing, okay? - Okay.
Ame?
不过 倘若大势果真如此
Although, if those wheels are in motion anyway,
那我确实需要早做准备 比如
then I would say go ahead and, you know,
收集情报 什麽的
put a file together, you know.
知道我最烦什麽吗?
You know what I'm sick of?
Chung可能把某人救出起火坦克的蠢故事
That stupid story of Chung supposedly pulling some guy out of a burning tank.
拜托 爲什麽军人行应尽义务都能得奖章?
Come on, why do guys in the army get a medal for doing their job?
那家伙依然严重烧伤了 就算真事 Chung也不够及时
The guy still had severe burns. If anything, Chung was too late.
喂喂 你的桌子在后面
Whoa, whoa. Your desk is in the back.
- 这是中立区 - 对 所以我征用了
- This is neutral territory. - Yep. So I'm claiming it.
- Sue 请告诉他侵权规则好吗? - 你觉得我是幼儿园老师吗 Mike?
Sue, would you like to tell him about the encroachment rules? Do I look like a kindergarten teacher to you, Mike?
- 说实话 没错 - 再说一遍?
- Actually, yes. - Excuse me?
呃 不 你不是 好吧 随你便
Uh, no, you don't. Okay, go ahead.
- 我去用你后面的桌子 - 做什麽用 配餐台?
- I'm gonna use your desk in the back. - As what, a pantry?
噢 找到了
Oh, here we go.
看谁来了 伙计们! 你们最爱的Jonah哟
Look who it is, everybody! It's your favorite Jonah.
你都不是你妈的最爱Jonah Jonah
You're not even your mom's favorite Jonah, Jonah.
别改"会见新闻界"的谈话要点 好吗? 我刚准备好
Don't be changing the talking points for my "Meet the Press" thing. Okay? I am prepped.
我是来传达总统的些微要求的
I come bearing a very minor request from the president.
他想用遥控器指挥我吗?
Does he want to operate me by remote control?
不 那在科技上不可能
No. That's not technologically possible.
呃 总统希望你不要过分强调革除"冗长辩论"
Um, potus would appreciate it if you didn't go too hard on filibuster reform.
你说什麽呢? 那是我最具代表性的 副总统改革行动
What are you talking about? That's my defining vice presidential crusade.
本任期仅专注于经济
The administration is totally focused on the economy.
- 周末愉快 好吗? - 夫人
- Have a great weekend, okay? - Ma'am.
- 夫人 你也是 - 嗯 谢谢你
- Ma'am, you, too. - Yeah, thank you very much.
- 夫人 - 我要去收拾东西了
- Ma'am. - I need to gather my things.
还有件事... 这些该加水了
I'll tell you something else... these need water, okay?
- 好吗? - 明白
- Got it. - Okay.
- 好 - 夫人 总统更希望你选择移民法案...
So, ma'am, potus would like your new chosen subject to be immigration reform...
美国公民被非法移民抢走工作 诸如此类
Americans losing jobs to illegals, et cetera.
我整个初期竞选都是爲移民特赦说话
I spoke in favor of immigration amnesty all during my primary campaign.
- 嘿 最近如何? - 无意冒犯 夫人
- Hey, how's it going? - Well, with respect, ma'am,
你真以爲有人记得你的初期竞选吗?
do you think anybody's gonna remember your primary campaign?
除了开头半句 我没察觉到
In spite of your preface, I did not detect
剩下的问题中有一丝尊重
a whole lot of respect in that question.
我的初衷是淡化选区的回忆
You know, I meant that more as a slight against
而非攻讦你的竞选效能
the power of recollection of the electorate and not as an attack on the potency of your campaign.
那爲什麽你不直接那麽说呢?
Well, why didn't you say that, then?
噢 因爲你的社交能力是狼教的
Oh, because you have the social skills of someone who was raised by wolves.
噢 还有把中国强调成贸易伙伴
Oh, and pump up China as a trading partner.
我们必须坚持强调这点
We gotta keep nudging that one along.
我该回白宫去了 天啊 我真喜欢这说法
I gotta get back to the White House. God, I love saying that.
天佑总统
Well, God bless the president, you know.
他真是个好人
I mean, he's really a great man,
但他真的让我彻底乳酸了
but he is busting my fuckin' lady balls here.
还有强调中国?
And pump up China?
那算是对Chung的刺探吗?
Is that some sort of dig about Chung?
好吧 我想我们回不了家了
Okay, so I guess we're not going home.
- 对 Sue? - 在
- Yeah. Sue? - Yep.
- 我们不走了 - 嗷
- We're staying. - Aw.
周日 早7:45 副总统官邸
- 周六晚上玩得开心吗? - 还不错
- Did you have a good Saturday night? - It was okay.
我的Leviathan拉链坏了
My zipper on my Leviathan broke,
我不得不开车到处找修理替换
so I had to drive around trying to find a replacement.
- 你怎麽过的? - 你问我怎麽过的? 我晚上7点上床
What did you do? You know what I did? I went to bed at 7:00 P.M.
晚上7点 还是周六晚 罹患疟疾的人都睡得比那晚
- Ooh. - 7:00 P.M. on a Saturday night. Even people who are dying of malaria stay up later than that.
他们睡不着的 因爲咳嗽
Well, they can't sleep because they're coughing.
嗨 伙计们 我准备好了 马上下来
Hi, guys. I'm all set. I'll be there in just a second.
- 好 好好好 - 明白
- Okay, yeah. Yeah, yeah. - All right.
我该走了 至于你嘛?
I gotta go, but you know what?
想呆多久呆多久 我完事给你打电话 好吗?
Hang out here as long as you like and I'll call you afterwards, okay?
- 我不能和你一起走吗? - 不 我不想他们看到你
Can't I just leave now with you? No, I don't want them to see you.
- 这些额外规程... 真是太怪了 - 我知道 但我可是副总统
All these extra rules... it's kind of weird. I know, but I am the vice president.
噢 对 你当然是
Oh, yes, you are.
听到你这麽说就让我性致勃发呢
Hearing you say that gives me a massive hard-on.
噢 我的确是副总统
Oh. I am the vice president.
噢 宝贝 我准备吃午餐了
Oh, baby, I'm ready to launch.
我准备吃你了
And I'm ready to eat you up.
噢 早上第二回 没想到你有这能耐呢
Oh, second breakfast. I didn't know you had it in you.
噢 老天 我真想水乳交融
Oh, God. Oh, I want it in me.
- 行了 - 拜
- All right. - Bye.
我要好好欣赏你的翘臀
Yeah. I'm gonna watch your ass move. Yeah.
- 嗨 伙计们 - 嘿
- Hi, you guys. - Hey.
- 你气色不错 - 噢 谢谢
- You look pretty. - Oh, thank you.
- 你们怎麽样? - 很好
- How are you guys? - Great.
- 准备好了? 都带齐了? - 噢 是的
- All set? You got everything? - Oh, yes.
- 我去拿点东西 - 你周六晚过得如何?
呃 还不赖
- I just have to get my stuff. - How was your Saturday night? Um, it was fine.
- 我帮你开 - 谢谢
- Here, I'll get that. - Thank you.
- Mike! - 噢 嘿
- Mike! - Oh, hey.
只是在想象你在"会见新闻界"上的完美发挥
Just visualizing you kicking ass on "Meet the Press."
你怎麽这麽累的样子? 你啥都没干
Why are you so tired? You don't do anything.
这是Scott对Chung的调查
Here's the research Scott pulled on Chung.
注意第一页
Check out page one.
他生于中国 然后他父亲才得到国籍
He was born back in China before his dad got his citizenship,
所以他不可能当总统或副总统
so he can't be president or vice president.
- 真的? 真是个好消息 - 嗯哼
- Really? - Mm-hmm. Well, that's good news.
- "会见新闻界"还有更多好消息 - 噢 真的?
- More good news for "Meet the Press." - Oh, yeah?
David Gregory生病了
David Gregory is ill.
- Sam Finnegan补缺 - 哈哈 雏儿一个
- Sam Finnegan is the fill-in. - Ho ho, a virgin.
我要把他吃干抹净了
Oh, God, I'm gonna eat him up.
怎麽了?
What?
- 那样体育话题就要改变了 - 别紧张
- Well, that changes the sports stuff. - No panic.
我们只需把红人改成Finnegan支持的球队
We'll just change the redskins to whatever Finnegan's team is.
- Finnegan支持哪个队? - 我确信他是芝加哥熊的粉丝
- What is Finnegan's team? - I'm pretty sure he's a Bears fan.
- 确信? - Mike 你确信? 那可帮不上忙
- Pretty sure? - Mike, you're pretty sure? Exactly. That doesn't help.
没关系 你要聊的是乌鸦队
It doesn't matter because you're gonna talk about the Ravens.
我知道我是乌鸦球迷
I know that I'm a Ravens fan,
但万一Finnegan也是乌鸦球迷呢 你明白吗?
but, like, what if Finnegan is a Ravens fan, too, you know?
- 一支队伍可玩不起来 对吧? - 电子游戏里就可以
A team can't play itself, can it? You can in video games.
有人说你的移民政策
Some people say your immigration policy
取决于你的就业计划
is at odds with your jobs program.
- 对此你怎麽回应? - 我会如此回应...
How would you respond to that? Well, I would respond like this...
我会说经济在我当初声明之后
I would say that the economy has changed a great deal
已经有明显转变 总统和我都同意
since I made those statements and the president and I agree
美国公民理当优先
that Americans have to come first.
干得好 完美的太极推手
That's my girl. Olympic-style backflip.
我强烈相信...
And I believe very strongly...
- 那是汗 人中的汗 - 那是反光
- That's sweat. That's lip sweat. - That's shimmer.
你今天没有怎麽提到 参议院革除"冗长辩论"计划
You haven't spoken much today about the Senate filibuster reform.
我这麽说吧... 要想做出变革
Well, I'll say this... in order to reform,
就要有所行动
you have to perform.
- 她把话题引到冗长辩论了! - 等Jonah 打来了
She got the filibuster in! Just waiting for Jonah. Here he is.
- 噢 真的? - 您好 男性外生殖器增大诊所
Oh, yeah? Hello, penis enlargement clinic.
Mike 到底是谁的失职 你还是她?
Mike, who is incompetent, you or her?
她现在说的可是革除"冗长辩论"
Because she just talked about filibuster reform.
他自己问她的
He asked her.
我的意向很简单 我的意向就是... 同意
My message is simple, my message is this... Yes.
- 谢谢 副总统女士 - 不客气
- Thank you, madam vice president. - Absolutely.
Sam 我得问你一下... 你是熊队球迷
Sam, I just have to ask you... you're a Bears fan.
- 对吧? - 被你看穿了
- Is that right? - Guilty.
- 她提了体育话题没? - 她现在在说
- She do the sports yet? - She's doing it now.
我们一点也不担心 有Flacco... 万事安矣
We're not nervous at all. With Flacco... forget about it.
我赌瓶啤酒 我们触底得分赢得比赛
I'll bet you a beer that we win by a T.D.
那Ray Rice? 他的优势也很大 (与Flacco同爲乌鸦队员)
What about Ray Rice? Hell of a lead runner.
Ray Rice Ray Rice Ray...
这个 他 呃... Ray Rice 他打得不错
Well, he, uh... Ray Rice, he play nice.
- 副总统 - 非常感谢
- Vice president. - Thank you so much.
我们下周再见
We'll be back next week,
因爲每逢周日 "会见新闻界"
because if it's Sunday, it's "Meet the Press."
你会看Danny Chung的"面对全国"节目吗?
Will you be watching Danny Chung on "Face the Nation"?
呃 我会的
Uh, you know, I would,
不过我还有牌局 所以我恐怕得跳过
but I've got a game of solitaire going on, so I think I'll give that a skip.
- 他掌管长期环城公路资金 很有总统潜力 - 噢 是吗?
Long-term beltway money's on him - as presidential material. - Oh, really?
那我会很吃惊的 严格说来他不算美国人
Well, I'd be surprised because technically he's not an American.
我是说 因爲他出生地不是这里
I mean, because he wasn't, um, born here,
不是因爲他是半个中国人...
you know, not because he's half Chine...
- 你懂的 因爲他的父母... - 我该走了
- You know, 'cause his parents... - Well, I've gotta go.
- 好吧 - 很荣幸能与你谈话
- Okay. - But it was a pleasure talking to you.
非常感谢 你弄好没?
Thank you so much. Did you get it?
- 搞定了 - 噢...
- I got it. - Oh...
他们没有录下 对吧? 我戴着麦克风 但我估计没开
Listen, they wouldn't have recorded that, right? I had the mic on, but I don't think it was hot.
- 你觉得它开着吗? - 我只能祈祷它没有
- Do you think that it was on? - I hope to God they didn't.
我没有说因爲他是半个中国人所以就是坏人
I didn't say he was bad because he's part Chinese.
- 没 没有 - 身爲中国人没什麽坏的
- No, no. - It's not bad to be Chinese.
- 你能和录音师谈谈吗? - 我不能 这样会显得小题大做
Can you go speak to the sound guy? I can't do it because it'll make it look like a thing.
我不可以小题大做
I don't wanna make it look like a thing,
- 也许我能... - 我来吧
so maybe I can... I'll do it.
不不不 Gary Gary
No, no, no. Gary, Gary, Gary.
- Gary Gary 过来 - 我去谈吧
Gary, come. - I'll do it.
- 我觉得他应该去和录音师谈谈 - 好吧
I think actually he should go talk to the sound guy. - Yeah. - Okay.
- 你知道我该怎麽说吗? - 你自告奋勇的 你没计划吗?
Do you have any ideas on what I should say? You offered to do this. What was your plan?
我的计划是过去了再见招拆招
My plan was to go over there and get some ideas on what to say.
Gary Gary 稍微提点一下就行
Gary, Gary, just give it a light touch.
- 别太深入 - 好
- No import to it. - Okay.
- 那是什麽意思? - 就和他聊聊
- What does that mean? - Just talk to him
同事和同事那种
like working guy to working guy.
- 随意一点 - 明白了 单对单
- It's casual. - Got it. Mano a mano.
- 好吧 - 噢 上帝啊
- Okay. - Oh, Jesus Christ.
即使用西班牙语 听起来也不像能奏效的感觉
Even in Spanish, you know, it doesn't sound like it's gonna work.
也许只是我太多心
It totally might have just been me,
不过... 最后是不是有点小问题什麽的?
but kind of... didn't it sound a little glitchy in the end or anything like that?
- 你是说我没尽职? - 不 天啊 不是的
- You saying I can't do my job? - No. Oh, God, no.
- 很糟吗? - 他刚从笑脸变成了苦瓜脸
It's bad? Well, he just went from a smiley guy to a frowny guy.
我只想确保一切正常 你懂的
I just need to know if everything's okay, you know.
同事对同事 你懂的
Working guy to working guy, you know.
- 听着 女同事 - 好吧
- Listen, working girl. - Okay.
我没听到任何问题
Yeah. I didn't hear any glitches.
我只听到一堆废话 了了?
All I heard was the sound of a fuckup, okay?
- 他完全是个外行 - 对
- He was completely out of his element. - Yeah.
我同意 我同意
I agree. I agree.
嘿 已经有媒体对此感兴趣了
Hey, we're getting some press interest in this already.
- 噢 天啊 - 在哪? 在哪?
- Oh, God. - Where? Where?
还没有定案 还没成定局
It's still non-narrative. No momentum yet.
夫人 鉴于现状 也许你需要我留在办公室里
Ma'am, I thought you might want me in the office, given the circumstances.
- 你怎麽知道现状如何的? - 我可是Sue
- How do you know about the circumstances? - Well, I'm Sue.
全知全能是我的工作 Amy
It's my job to know everything, Amy.
- 所以肯定是传扬开来了? - 不 不 不是传扬的那种开来
So it's definitely out there out there? No, no, it's not out there out there.
我听说了 Dan 就是传扬的那个开来 所以我才会留在这个其中 Dan
I heard about it, Dan, so it sort of is out there out there. That's why I'm in here in here, Dan.
- Jonah来了 Jonah来了 - 噢 该死!
- Jonah's coming. Jonah's coming. - Oh, fuck!
- 嘘! - 好吧 我该怎麽办?
- Shh! - All right, what do I do?
万一他不知道是传扬的那样开来? 我该跟他说什麽?
What if he doesn't know that it's not definitely out there out there? Should I tell him that?
你不会想把把柄给那个人形炸弹的
You don't wanna give a loaded gun to that walking silo.
- 别太当回事 除非真的出大事 - 你有没有...
- Don't make it a thing until it's a thing. - Do you have any...
坏消息 伙计们
Bad news, everyone.
- 此事还未流到主流媒体... - 那是断章取义
This hasn't hit the mainstream media yet... It was out of context.
但是弗吉尼亚州的Portsmouth 有吊臂断裂砸到了船
But a crane has collapsed onto a ship at Portsmouth, Virginia.
噢 感谢... 神啊 太可怕了
Oh, thank... God, how horrible.
等等 什麽是断章取义?
Wait, what was out of context?
我们以爲你要唠叨革除"冗长辩论"的事
Um, we thought you were gonna give me shit about filibuster reform.
噢 白宫还不是很清楚此事
Oh, well, the White House is very much under the moon
不过我们重申一遍
about that, but let's reboot.
总统只坚持经济问题
The president is stuck in economic talks.
- 我们需要副统亲场 - 需要什麽? 副总统亲自到场
- We need a V.P.V.P. - A what? A vice presidential visual presence.
你不能生造缩略词 Jonah
You can't just make up acronyms, Jonah.
- 总得有人去做 Mike - 不 没人会做
Somebody has to, Mike. - No, they don't.
呃 好吧 我们该赶过去了
Uh, okay, well, then, we should head on down there.
- 我们快行动吧 尽快赶到 - 谢谢 谢谢
- Let's get the ball rolling - Thank you. Thank you.
我们会处理好的
.let's get there as soon as possible Yeah, we've got it handled.
噢 Jonah 这身很衬你
Oh, Jonah, that's a good look for you.
你管这身叫什麽? 双便服?谢了 Mike 不过今天周日
What do you call that? Bi-casual? Thanks, Mike, but it's Sunday.
我工作努力迅速 腿部热量积蓄 所以我决定随风飘荡一下
I work hard, I work fast, and I get hot legs. I say let the whale hang loose.
- 我招谁惹谁了? - 举手表决
- Who am I offending? - Show of hands.
都有
Right here.
好吧 我猜我们应付得不错
O- kay, well, I think that worked out pretty good.
刚刚证实... 目前2人遇难 24人受伤
Just confirmed... Two fatalities, 24 injured so far.
我不是那个意思 Dan 我们得去趟医院
I didn't mean it like that. Dan, we're going to a hospital.
你有没有能换的正装?
Do you have a suit you can change into?
- 我有5套 - 好吧
- I have five. - Okay.
你有没有不是圣诞老人服
Do you have something that can fit
而且能让McClintock穿得下的?
the McClintock shape that's not a Santa suit?
- 我会找到的 - 我们要去医院
I got something. We're going to a hospital.
可不是万圣节要糖果
We're not going trick or treating.
- 副总统女士... - 是的
- Madam vice president... - Yes.
这是Ashley 医院院长
This is Ashley, the hospital administrator.
谢谢你能来 这意义很重大
Thank you so much for coming. It really means a lot.
- 谢谢 - 我跟你说...
- Thank you. - Well, let me tell you something...
因爲美国人民在这里出现 是职位赋予我的特权之一
being here for the American people is one of the privileges of this job.
- 当然了 这是一项悲哀的特权 - 是的
- It's a sad privilege, of course... - Yes.
但不管怎样也是一项特权
But it's a privilege nonetheless.
女士 我不知道这些人是不是都活着
Ma'am, I don't know if all these people are bereaving,
- 所以你就正常聊天就好了 好吗? - 好的
- so just converse generally, okay? - Right.
- 正常聊天? 聊什麽? 聊天气吗? - 不是天气
Converse generally? What about? The weather? Not about the weather.
不过现在确实是反季节高温天气 是吧?
It is unseasonably warm, though, okay?
副总统女士 要是你跟我来的话 我会给你介绍一些家庭
So, madam vice president, if you'll just come with me, I'll show you to some of our families.
嗯 怎麽安排都行
Oh, well, however I can be of service.
你好吗 先生? 噢 天哪 你伤得真重
How do you do, sir? Oh, my goodness, you got so hurt.
- 这是家很好的医院对吧? - 是的 女士
- Well, it's a great hospital, isn't it? - Yes, ma'am.
天哪 看你的脖子 先生 千万别转头
Oh, dear, look at your neck. Hi, sir. Don't turn your head.
我来握握你的手
I'll give you a little squeeze on your hand.
- 嗯 你看起来还挺好 - 其实我不好
- Well, you seem just fine. - I'm not really.
- 内伤 - 内伤 嗯
- Internal. - Internal. Hmm.
这是家属...他们在等儿子的消息
This is a family... they're waiting to hear about their son.
- 噢 - 等等 不不 还不到时候
- Oh. - Hold on. No, no, not yet.
这是私人时间 不是照相的时候
This is a private moment. This is not a photo op.
- 世界变化快啊 - 嗯
- It's amazing how the world changes. - Mm.
上一分钟你还在享受美妙的阳光...
One minute, you're enjoying this amazing sunshine...
呃 现在是反季节高温
Well, it's unseasonably warm.
下一分钟 你的世界就支离破碎了
And the next, your whole world's gone to pieces.
- 噢 天哪 - 这是给他动手术的大夫
- Oh, gosh. - This is his surgeon.
- 你好吗 先生? - Graber医生
- How do you do, sir? - Dr. Graber.
- 医生 我儿子有消息吗? - Sam会挺过来的
Any news, doctor, about our son? Sam's going to make it.
好了 同学们 我这里有料了
Okay, guys, I got a little sound bite for y'all to nibble on right here.
- 噢 这太好了 - 非常好
- Oh, that is just fantastic. - Very good.
医生 我们感谢你的辛勤工作
Doctor, we appreciate your hard work.
- 好消息 - 我只是想说 太感谢你们
- Good news. - I just wanna say how grateful we are
这些优秀的医生和护士了
to all of our most capable doctors and nurses.
太感谢了
So grateful.
而且我也要说 如果我们发现
And I'd also like to say if, for some reason, we find out
这样的意外是由某些人的疏忽而造成的话
that there was negligence that caused this accident,
那些负有责任的人
those who are responsible
必须要向白宫交待
are gonna have the White House to answer to.
- 就是! - 就是这样
- Yeah! - That's right.
谢谢你能来这里 副总统女士
Thank you for being here, madam vice president.
- 你是个好女人 - 是的!
- You are a good woman. - Yeah!
你不怕说出自己的想法
And you're not afraid to say what's on your mind.
- 噢 - Danny Chung...
- Oh. - Danny Chung...
我...我一直努力尽量诚实
I... I always try to speak as honestly as I can.
我听见你说那些人的话了 我会投票给你的
I heard what you said about those people. You'd get my vote.
因爲严格来说他不是美国人 (奥观海同志中枪了)
'Cause technically he's n an American.
我是说...
I mean...
他们接管了我们的口岸 就像是他们在侵略我们一样
They're taking over our ports. It's like they've invaded us.
是啊 现在他们觉得他们可以做总统了?
Yeah, and now they think they can be president?
- 没门! - 这是白宫 不是黄宫!
- No way! - Come on, this is the White House, not the Yellow House.
加油 Selina!
Come on, Selina!
U.S.A.! U.S.A.! U.S.A.!
你得马上给Chung打电话 Amy
You have to get Chung on the phone right away, Amy.
- 把这个事了结掉 Amy - 是 正在打
- Shut this thing down, Amy. - Yeah, dialing now.
好了 他接了
Here, he's picking up.
- 什麽? 我... - 噢 你好
- What? I... - Oh. Hello.
是的 副总统在线上等你
Hi. Yes, I have the vice president for you.
州长吗? 嗨 你好吗?
Governor? Hi. How are you?
我不...我不知道你看了今天的
I don't... I don't know if you saw the footage today
"会见新闻界"没有?
from "Meet the Press,"
但是那不是我的本意 而且那也不是我真正的想法
but, you know, that is not what I meant and it certainly isn't what I think.
- Gary 可以等会再系安全带 - 那我们这麽说吧...
- Gary, the belt can wait. - Let's just put it this way...
当时我真正想说的是...我的苍天啊!
what I was trying to say was... Jesus Christ!
- 上帝啊! 噢! - 噢 天哪
Oh, my God! Oh!
Gary 你刚才把我的肉...
Oh, God. Gary, that was my fucking flesh that you just...
- 你好? - 给按进去了
- Hello? - ...trapped in there.
- 语音信箱了 接着打 - 对不起
- Voice mail. Keep trying. - I'm so sorry.
- 好了 你够了 - 好的
- All right, that's enough. - Okay.
(副总统)很长一段时间之内都不能出席
there is not gonna be a lot of availability for a while.
Jennifer 说实话 我家的窗子都比 副总统现在的时间表安排空位多
Jennifer, quite frankly, I had more windows in my first apartment than the V.P. currently has in her schedule.
- 怎麽了? - 好吧 你知道吗?
- What's going on? - Well, you know what?
如果Chung州长不回电话的话 我可以以藐视本办公室灭了他
If governor Chung doesn't call back, I can just take him down for disrespecting the office.
- 这个怎麽样? - 可以
- How about that? - Yes.
我们刚才流失了革除"冗长辩论"的支持者
We just lost the numbers on filibuster reform.
- 你刚才说什麽? - 是的 是的
- What did you just say? - Yeah, yeah.
Doyle参议员刚刚收回对你的支持
Senator Doyle has just withdrawn his support.
因爲Amy在Chung的新书发布会上说的一些话
Something Amy said at Chung's book launch.
他还在爲绿色産业而生气
He was still upset about clean jobs,
这个是你的责任 Dan 因爲你把Sidney Purcell放到工作小组里了
which is on you, Dan, because you put Sidney Purcell on the task force.
是啊! 你知道吗? 我要怪的是乔治华盛顿!
Oh, sure! You know what? I blame George Washington.
如果不是他创立了现在政府的形式 那我们就不用...
If he hadn't started this whole form of government,
好吧 好吧 别吵了!
- then we wouldn't...- Okay, okay, stop squabbling!
我现在应该怎麽做?
What am I supposed to do now?
告诉我
Tell me that.
我应不应该给Doyle打电话求他回心转意?
I'm supposed to call Doyle and beg him to come back?
我是美国副总统 你们这帮大傻逼!
I'm the vice president of the United States, you stupid little fuckers!
应该是这些人来求我!
These people should be begging me!
这个门的高度应该减一半
That door should be half its height
这样来我办公室的人就得他娘的跪着了!
so that people can only approach me in my office on their goddamn, motherfucking knees.
我不能失去Doyle
I can't lose Doyle.
- 谁手里还有一把参议员? - 和Doyle划清界限吧 当他是在唬你
Who else has a bucketful of senators? Cut Doyle loose, all right? Call his bluff.
- 我们转换阵营去接触移民改革党团 - 什麽?
We reach across the aisle - to the immigration reform caucus. - What?
你想不想顺便摆脱大白人挑剔的形象 女士?
You want to break out the white, pointy hoods, too, ma'am?
听着 我们只要给他们党团几个承诺
Look, we throw them a few commitments to their cause
以此换取他们对革除"冗长辩论"的支持
in exchange for support on filibuster reform.
- 这很容易... - 呃
- This is easy. - Ugh.
你只要踏上了那条黑道 什麽幺蛾子都会有
Once you go down that dark country road, the lights go out and the scarecrows come to life.
有人想听班卓琴吗?
Yeah, anyone hear the banjo music?
听着 Mike 你老听那种音乐 是因爲你丫脑子被门板夹了
Look, Mike, that's what you always hear because mentally you're in a fuckin' hammock on a back porch.
- Dan 这可不是梦幻政坛 - 住口! 住口!
Dan, this isn't fantasy politics. Stop it! Stop it!
这对你来说既是参议院改革的胜利
This is a win for you on Senate reform
也是另一场对总统在移民政策上的胜利 对吧?
and it's also another big win for you with the president on immigration, all right?
大胜 大胜!
Win big, win big.
我不知道...也许你和Dan应该去和...
I don't know... maybe you and Dan should go down and talk to...
呃...我去...亚利桑那州参议员谈一谈
J... God damn it... the senator from Arizona.
就是那个想对穿披风的人随机搜查的那个
The one who wants to random search people in ponchos?
- 噢 Bill - O'Brien
- Oh, Bill. - O'Brien.
- 对 - 对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
他和那些白人至上党团老眉来眼去的
He's got a lot of sway with the pro-Caucasian caucus.
好吧 那我们有了O'Brien 他可以带来McCaulay和Cunliffe
All right, so we get O'Brien, who brings us McCaulay and Cunliffe.
McCaulay是那个鼻毛长得像 有浣熊住鼻孔里的那位麽?
Is McCaulay the one with the nose hair problem like he's got two raccoons in his nostrils?
那就是7票对Doyle的5票 那就是"冗长辩论"派的绝杀啊
That's seven to Doyle's five. I mean, this is a filibuster slam dunk.
- Chung在直播电视节目上 - 什麽?!
- Chung is on TV live. - What?!
- 快打开 快打开 - 遥控器呢?
- Get it on. Get it on. - Where's the remote?
在碗里 遥控器在碗里
It's in the bowl. The remote's in the bowl.
Sue 按按乐在哪里?
Sue, where's the clicker?
- 按按乐在哪里? - 同志们 在书柜里呢
- Where's the clicker? - Guys, it's in the credenza.
拿来 快 快 快
Get it. Quick, quick, quick.
- 什麽频道? 频道? - 直播的都行
- What channel? Channel? - Any live TV.
Mike...不 Mike 别碰那个遥控器 搞不好你要发射原子弹的
Mike... no, Mike. Don't touch that remote. You're gonna launch a nuke or something.
- Sue? - 这是关于今天早些时候评论所做的简单回应
- Sue? - A few brief words about the comments that were made earlier today.
尽管在互联网上有一些阴暗的流言
Despite what is said in some dark corners of the Internet,
但在我出生的时候
when I was born, both my parents
我的父母都是完全的归化美国公民
were fully naturalized American citizens.
什麽 他是他妈的美国队长吗?
What? He's Captain fuckin' America?
- 现在怎麽了? 干得好啊 Amy - 这不是...
- What's happening here? Good job, Amy. - It's not...
这不是Scott给我的信息
That is not the information I was given by Scott.
这说明了她手下职员调查技术的透彻性
A quiet word with one of her staff regarding the thoroughness of their research techniques.
到底Scott用的是什麽调查工具? 是他娘的苦力报告吗?
What did Scott use as a research tool, the fuckin' drudge report?
- 二代美籍华裔 - 那个加上卫生间的墙
Second-generation Chinese American... That and bathroom walls.
自豪到足以爲了这个国家抛头颅洒热血
Proud enough to risk my life for this country.
我胸前有一颗紫色的心
I've got a purple heart on my chest,
但在我胸腔里跳动的那颗 却是红白蓝色的
but the one that beats inside of me is red, white, and blue.
- 噢 不 他真说得出口 - 他抓住了机会
- No, he didn't. He didn't say that. - He is seizing his moment.
这也是爲什麽 这个国家是地球上最伟大的国家
And that's why this is the greatest country on earth.
我现在能吐出一条腿来
I am gonna throw up a leg.
然后我会捡起那条腿 用它打死Scott
And then I'm gonna take that leg and I'm gonna beat Scott to death with it.
- Scott! - 啊
- Scott! - Ah!
我会起草一封道歉信给明尼苏达之王 也就是Chung州长
I'm gonna go draft a letter of apology to the king of Minnesota, governor Chung.
现在我们要做的是 Mike 好好给Chung道歉
Here's what we're gonna do... Mike, big fat apology to Chung;
Amy 搞定Doyle 我要这一票
Amy, fuck Doyle. I want this bill.
你们去和O'Brien好好谈谈 拿下边境党团
You guys talk to O'Brien and get that border caucus.
- 好的 - Amy 穿上你的舞鞋 马上去边境
- Okay. - Amy, put on your dancing shoes and head for the border right now.
- 快去 - 不 我不去
- Go on. - No, I'm not doing it.
快点动起来
Get a move on.
- 他们来了 - 开始吧
This is them. Here we go.
你好 O'Brien参议员 我是Dan Egan 我们通过电话了 很高兴见到你 先生
Hi, senator O'Brien. I'm Dan Egan. We spoke on the phone. A pleasure to meet you, sir.
好吧 我不知道你是谁 所以我还不知道该不该高兴
Well, I have no idea who you are, so I don't know whether it's a pleasure or not.
- 好吧 - 这是Jack
- Okay. - This is Jack.
- 你好 Jack - 你好
- Hi, Jack. - Hi.
Amy Brookheimer 副总统的幕僚长
Amy Brookheimer, vice president's chief of staff.
长官? 应该是女长官吧?
Chief? Shouldn't that be chiefess?
别紧张 小姐 我只是开玩笑
Relax, missy. I'm just yanking your chain.
当然了
Absolutely.
这地方不错 不是吗?
This place looks nice, huh?
这里的牛小排好像很不错 但在我们点菜之前
Looks like they do a mighty fine plate of ribs, but before we do any ordering,
我想知道你们会不会说一些琐碎的事来扫兴
I'd like to know if you're going to offend us
如果是这样 我们就不用吃东西 直接走了
with some chickenshit deal that means we have to leave before the food comes.
尽管点菜吧
You're fine to order.
我感觉糟透了
I feel so horrible.
你知道吗 就像我下令解决某人
You know, it's like I've ordered a hit on somebody.
而现在只能等他们打电话告诉我任务完成了
I'm just waiting for the call to say that it's done.
任务完成
It's done.
你想来杯酒吗? 或者喝杯水? 或者...洗手液?
Do you want a glass of wine? You want some water? You want some hand sanitiz...
- 我需要安静 - 安静
- I want quiet. - Quiet?
再见 Scott 你的职业生涯到头了
So long, Scott. You are professionally dead.
祝你今晚愉快
Have a nice evening.
在上东区
Up here on the eastern seaboard,
人们很容易忘记 我们国家有很大一块地方
it's easy to forget what a big slice of our country rubs shoulders
还和一个名叫墨西哥的失败国家有来往
with a failed state by the name of Mexico.
听着 如果你有个糟糕的邻居 每晚都跑到你的院子里
Now, if you had bad neighbors who came into your yard every night
弄一些药和豆子在你的花上面
to crap a buttful of drugs and beans on your flowers,
你应该会考虑建一个围栏
you might think about building a fence.
我们不可能建边境围栏 好吗?
You're not gonna get a border fence, all right?
那可是一条3000英里长的围栏
You're talking about a 3,000-mile-long fence.
对建筑业来说是好事啊
Great for the construction industry.
是啊 但讽刺的是 我们只请得起移民工人来做这个
Yeah, but ironically, the only affordable option would be immigrant labor.
嗯 我的选民已经厌倦了
Well, my constituents are fed up
在自己的国家却感到寡不敌衆
with feeling outnumbered in their own country.
伙计们 在保持美国的特性这个问题上
Fellas, we shouldn't have a problem
我们不该有什麽问题
working to preserve a certain kind of American identity.
是啊
Yes.
亲爱的 如果你继续这麽说 晚餐结束以后我们还能一起抽雪茄
Now you keep talking like that, sweetheart, and we'll be having cigars at the end of this dinner.
只要不是古巴的就行
Just not Cuban ones.
天哪
Oh, my God,
- 今天真是糟透了 - 是吗?
- I am having the shittiest day. - Yeah?
- 有什麽能让我高兴的吗? - 确实有
You got anything to make me feel better? I do indeed.
- 什麽? - 嗯...
- What is it? - Well...
大概7英吋长 在我两腿之间...
It's about seven inches, hangs between my legs...
- 那玩意 - 我喜欢叫他Ted士官
The thing. I like to call him sergeant Ted.
好吧 你告诉Ted士官
Okay, well, you tell sergeant Ted
我希望他可以
I would like him very much
在我的椭圆办公室里训练我
to drill me in my oval office.
事实上 我希望他
In fact, I need him to put the finger
把手指放在扣子上
on the button
然后到我的玫瑰园里来
and come into my rose garden.
士官已经立正了
The sergeant is standing at attention.
你知道吗 我现在就过去 马上
You know what... I'm coming over there, like, right away.
呃 你来的时候能偷偷溜进来吗?
Uh, you know, when you come over, can you try and sneak in incognito?
我的韩国邻居不会乐意看到我和你约会的
I got Korean neighbors and I don't think they'd like the idea of me dating you.
这是玩笑还是什麽? 一点都不好笑 闭嘴 Ted
Is that some kind of a joke or something? It's not funny at all. Fuck off, Ted.
我不懂你爲什麽要说...
I mean, I don't know why you would s...
- 你在...你在打电话吗? - 嗯哼
- You were... you were on the phone? - Mm-hmm.
- 我什麽都没听到 - 你最好什麽都没听到
- Oh, I didn't hear anything. - You better not have heard anything.
我什麽都没说
I didn't say anything.
天哪
Oh, my God.
真他妈的... 嘿 Jonah
Oh, for fuck sakes. Hey, Jonah.
- 你的紧身短裤呢? - 噢 紧身短裤会産生一些负面的牵引
What happened to your hot pants? Oh, the hot pants picked up some negative traction.
我觉得它不适合在办公室穿
I realize now they're unbecoming of my office.
我只是来看看和Chung州长直接的误会解除没
I'm just coming in to see if the misunderstanding with governor Chung has been resolved.
是啊 一切都好 好极了 好得不能再好了
Yeah. It's all fine and dandy and fabulous.
很好 那我回去继续享受周日了
Excellent. Well, then, I'm gonna go enjoy what's left of my Sunday.
我正在看约翰格里森姆的新书 太棒了 你也应该看看
I got the latest Grisham on the go and it's just awesome. You should read...
在提出财政申请的同时
As well as the funding request,
我们还能保证 副总统会反对
we can offer a commitment that the vice president will oppose immunity
对居留期超过五年的非法移民的豁免
for any illegal immigrants who have been here for more than five years.
嗯 现在这样才比较合我们心意
Well, now you're singing a tune that we may dance to.
- 我们只是... - 她还会游说总统
- Well, we just... - And she will lobby the president
并且公开表示支持你的立场
and express public support for your position.
好了 我回家了 我要回去大干一场
All right, I'm going home. I'm getting fucked every which way.
- Sue 总统来过电话吗? - 没
- Sue, did the president call? - No.
如果你能够履行这些 我会用爱我的傻儿子的热情
If you can deliver that, I will appear to love filibuster reform
去支持革除"冗长辩论"
as much as I appear to love my idiot son.
而看在我老婆的份上
And for my wife's sake,
我看起来像是爱极了那个可怜的白痴
I appear to love that wretched shitnia lot.
晚安 走吧 Jack
Good night. Let's go, Jack.
很高兴你们终于学会了...妥协
Good to see you guys could learn a new word today... compromise.
怎麽样? 咱们各让一步?
What do you say? Meet me halfway?
我今晚肯定睡不着了 太黑暗了
I'm not gonna be able to sleep tonight. That was fuckin' dark.
- 你比我估计的还多上了10层 - 这样一来 我就得下100层了
You've gone up 10 levels in my estimation, by the way. Which means I've gone down 100 in my own.
有时候爲了上升 你必须先下降
Sometimes you've gotta go down to go up.
喂 这次是我功劳
Eh... I am taking the credit for this.
是我打通了这条路 得到了这份肮脏的荣誉 所以由我来告诉Selina这个好消息
I tunneled through the shit, I get the dirty glory. It is me who tells Selina the good news.
- 副总统呢? - 回家了
Where is the vice president? She has gone home for the evening.
- 爲什麽? - 关于"大干一场"吧
Why? Something about "getting fucked every which way."
- 直接引用她的话 - 天哪 是的 我听到她讲电话了
Direct quote. Oh, God, yeah. I heard something on the phone.
- 天哪 天哪 - 她能承受多少次啊?
Oh, God. Oh, God. How many times can she be underneath that?
她的身体这麽小 而那男人好像很大
She's got such a little body and he seemed like a big man.
- 谁 他是谁? - 喂喂喂 能不能聊点别的?
Who? Who's he? Hey, hey, somebody talk about something else?
- 什麽都行 - 我得想点别的
Anything. Yeah, I gotta get these images out of my head.
我们能聊聊...我不知道...
Can we talk about... I don't know...
- 最喜欢的乐队 或者别的什麽 行吗? - 好啊 Mike 除了老鹰乐队你还喜欢什麽?
our favorite band or something, please? Yes. Who else are you into, Mike, apart from the Eagles?
呃 伟大的死亡(著名美国摇滚乐队)
Uh, grateful dead.
噢 那也是你最喜欢的妓院的名字 不是吗?
Oh, that's the name of your favorite whorehouse, too, right?
呃 等不及回家去烧掉这身衣服了
Ugh, can't wait to get home and burn my clothes.
别他妈把衣服弄坏了 Mike
Don't fuck up that suit, Mike.
- 好吧 晚安 Sue - 晚安 Gary
- All right, good night, Sue. - Good night, Gary.
晚安 Dan 上帝啊
Good night, Dan. Jesus Christ.
Dan 我给你十秒钟 别再让我分心了
Dan, you have about 10 seconds to stop distracting me,
不然他们就会在沙发后面发现你的尸体
or the next thing that they'll find at the back of that couch are your remains.
如果你不介意 我可以去副总统办公室里头坐着
If you like, I can go sit in the vice president's office.
什麽?
Excuse me?